Abitibi ManagementUnit O
River ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Paul ContactName B-PERSON
Fantin ContactName I-PERSON
, ContactName I-PERSON
R.P.F. ContactName E-PERSON
Abitibi Company B-ORG
River Company I-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Management Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
544 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
2828 Phone I-PHONE
ext Phone I-PHONE
. Phone I-PHONE
223 Phone E-PHONE
paul.fantin Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
frmg.ca Email E-EMAIL

Algoma ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Vince ContactName B-PERSON
Strack ContactName E-PERSON
Clergue Company B-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Management Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
Silviculture Title O
and Title O
Operations Title O
Forester Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
942 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
7706 Phone I-PHONE
ext Phone I-PHONE
. Phone I-PHONE
1 Phone E-PHONE
vince.strack Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
clergue.com Email E-EMAIL

Big ManagementUnit O
Pic ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Carmelo ContactName B-PERSON
Notarbartolo ContactName E-PERSON
Nawiinginokiima Company B-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Management Company I-ORG
Corporation Company E-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
807 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
229 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
8118 Phone I-PHONE
ext Phone I-PHONE
. Phone I-PHONE
11 Phone E-PHONE
carmelo.notarbartolo Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
nfmcforestry.ca Email E-EMAIL

Gordon ManagementUnit O
Cosens ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Darren ContactName B-PERSON
Ethier ContactName E-PERSON
Rayonier Company B-ORG
Advanced Company I-ORG
Materials Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O
, Title O
North Title O
Ontario Title O
West Title O
FRM Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
337 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
9784 Phone E-PHONE
darren.ethier Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
rayonieram.com Email E-EMAIL

Hearst ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Desneiges ContactName B-PERSON
Larose ContactName E-PERSON
Hearst Company B-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Management Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
362 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
4464 Phone I-PHONE
ext.1 Phone I-PHONE
( Phone I-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
372 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
3848 Phone E-PHONE
d_larose Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
hearstforest.com Email E-EMAIL

Magpie ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
John ContactName B-PERSON
Peluch ContactName E-PERSON
Wawa Company B-ORG
District Company E-ORG
MNRF Title O
District Title O
Manager Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
856 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
4703 Phone E-PHONE
john.peluch Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
ontario.ca Email E-EMAIL

Martel ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Chris ContactName B-PERSON
Grant ContactName E-PERSON
Tembec Company S-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O
- Title O
North Title O
Ontario Title O
East Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
864 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
3002 Phone E-PHONE
chris.grant Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
tembec.com Email E-EMAIL

Nagagami ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Carlo ContactName B-PERSON
Bin ContactName E-PERSON
Nagagami Company B-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Management Company I-ORG
Ltd. Company E-ORG
President Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
807 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
868 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
2426 Phone E-PHONE
carlobin Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
hornepaynelumber.com Email E-EMAIL

Nipissing ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Mark ContactName B-PERSON
Lockhart ContactName E-PERSON
Nipissing Company B-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Resource Company I-ORG
Management Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
752 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
5430 Phone I-PHONE
ext Phone I-PHONE
. Phone I-PHONE
21 Phone I-PHONE
( Phone I-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
499 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
6275 Phone E-PHONE
mlockhart Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
nipissingforest.com Email E-EMAIL

Northshore ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
William ContactName B-PERSON
Moryto ContactName E-PERSON
Northshore Company B-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
869 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
4020 Phone I-PHONE
ext Phone I-PHONE
. Phone I-PHONE
263 Phone E-PHONE
william.moryto Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
eacom.ca Email E-EMAIL

Pineland ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Jennifer ContactName B-PERSON
Tallman ContactName E-PERSON
EACOM Company B-ORG
Timber Company I-ORG
Corporation Company E-ORG
Chief Title O
Forester Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
267 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
3339 Phone I-PHONE
ext Phone I-PHONE
. Phone I-PHONE
227 Phone E-PHONE
jennifer.tallman Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
eacom.ca Email E-EMAIL

Romeo ManagementUnit O
Malette ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Chris ContactName B-PERSON
Grant ContactName E-PERSON
Tembec Company S-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O
- Title O
North Title O
Ontario Title O
East Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
864 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
3002 Phone E-PHONE
chris.grant Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
tembec.com Email E-EMAIL

Romeo ManagementUnit O
Malette ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Alan ContactName B-PERSON
Thorne ContactName E-PERSON
Tembec Company S-ORG
Chief Title O
Forester Title O
, Title O
Ontario Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
360 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
1280 Phone E-PHONE
alan.thorne Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
tembec.com Email E-EMAIL

Spanish ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Jennifer ContactName B-PERSON
Tallman ContactName E-PERSON
EACOM Company B-ORG
Timber Company I-ORG
Corporation Company E-ORG
Chief Title O
Forester Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
267 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
3339 Phone I-PHONE
ext Phone I-PHONE
. Phone I-PHONE
227 Phone E-PHONE
jennifer.tallman Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
eacom.ca Email E-EMAIL

Sudbury ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Mark ContactName B-PERSON
Lockhart ContactName E-PERSON
The Company B-ORG
Vermilion Company I-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Management Company I-ORG
Company Company I-ORG
Ltd. Company E-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
752 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
5430 Phone I-PHONE
ext Phone I-PHONE
. Phone I-PHONE
21 Phone I-PHONE
( Phone I-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
499 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
6275 Phone E-PHONE
mlockhart Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
nipissingforest.com Email E-EMAIL

Temagami ManagementUnit O
Mitch ContactName B-PERSON
Baldwin ContactName E-PERSON
North Company B-ORG
Bay Company I-ORG
District Company E-ORG
MNRF Title O
District Title O
Manager Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
475 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
5599 Phone E-PHONE
mitch.baldwin Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
ontario.ca Email E-EMAIL

Timiskaming ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Yves ContactName B-PERSON
Vivier ContactName E-PERSON
Timiskaming Company B-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Alliance Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
General Title O
Manager Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
544 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
2828 Phone I-PHONE
( Phone I-PHONE
705 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
544 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
3368 Phone E-PHONE
yves.viver Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
frmg.ca Email E-EMAIL

White ManagementUnit O
River ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Don ContactName B-PERSON
Larmer ContactName E-PERSON
White Company B-ORG
River Company I-ORG
Forest Company I-ORG
Products Company I-ORG
LP Company E-ORG
Superintendent Title O
Forest Title O
Planning Title O
and Title O
Compliance Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
807 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
822 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
1818 Phone I-PHONE
ext Phone I-PHONE
. Phone I-PHONE
220 Phone E-PHONE
don.larmer Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
wrfp.ca Email E-EMAIL

NORTHWEST ManagementUnit O
REGION ManagementUnit O
None ContactName O
None Company O
None Title O
None Phone O
None Email O

Black ManagementUnit O
Spruce ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Tom ContactName B-PERSON
Ratz ContactName E-PERSON
Resolute Company B-ORG
FP Company I-ORG
Canada Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
Forestry Title O
Manager Title O
, Title O
Ontario Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
807 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
475 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
7706 Phone E-PHONE
tom.ratz Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
resolutefp.com Email E-EMAIL

Caribou ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Tom ContactName B-PERSON
Ratz ContactName E-PERSON
Resolute Company B-ORG
FP Company I-ORG
Canada Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
Forestry Title O
Manager Title O
, Title O
Ontario Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
807 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
475 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
7706 Phone E-PHONE
tom.ratz Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
resolutefp.com Email E-EMAIL

English ManagementUnit O
River ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Tom ContactName B-PERSON
Ratz ContactName E-PERSON
Resolute Company B-ORG
FP Company I-ORG
Canada Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
Forestry Title O
Manager Title O
, Title O
Ontario Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
807 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
475 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
7706 Phone E-PHONE
tom.ratz Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
resolutefp.com Email E-EMAIL

Ogoki ManagementUnit O
Forest ManagementUnit O
Chris ContactName B-PERSON
Magee ContactName E-PERSON
Nipigon Company B-ORG
District Company E-ORG
MNRF Title O
District Title O
Manager Title O
( Phone B-PHONE
807 Phone I-PHONE
) Phone I-PHONE
887 Phone I-PHONE
- Phone I-PHONE
5013 Phone E-PHONE
chris.magee Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
ontario.ca Email E-EMAIL

