Artscape Organization S-ORG
Creative TargetIndustry O
Not Governance O
- Governance O
for Governance O
- Governance O
profit Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.torontoartscape.org Website O
. Website O
171 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
East StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Liberty StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Suite Unit B-ADDRESS
224 Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M6 PostalCode B-ADDRESS
K PostalCode I-ADDRESS
3P6 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Executive Title O
Assistant Title O
to Title O
the Title O
President Title O
and Title O
CEO Title O
Erin Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Breau Contact-FirstName B-PERSON
- Contact-FirstName I-PERSON
Barkley Contact-FirstName E-PERSON
416 Telephone B-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
392 Telephone I-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
1038 Telephone E-PHONE
erin Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
torontoartscape.on.ca Email E-EMAIL

Bitcoin Organization B-ORG
Decentral Organization I-ORG
Accelerate Organization E-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Private Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.bdaccelerate.com Website O
64 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Spadina StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Ave StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5V PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2H8 PostalCode I-ADDRESS
â€Ž PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Managing Title O
Director Title O
and Title O
partner Title O
A. Contact-LastName B-PERSON
Traviss Contact-LastName E-PERSON
Corry Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
info Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
BDAccelerate.com Email E-EMAIL

BrightSpark Organization B-ORG
Ventures Organization E-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Private Governance O
Accelerator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.brightspark.com Website O
2323 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Yonge StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Suite Unit B-ADDRESS
502 Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M4P PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2C9 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
None Title O
None Contact-LastName O
None Contact-FirstName O
416 Telephone B-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
488 Telephone I-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
1999 Telephone E-PHONE
info Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
brightspark.com Email E-EMAIL

CEO Organization B-ORG
Fusion Organization E-ORG
Mixed TargetIndustry O
Not Governance O
- Governance O
for Governance O
- Governance O
profit Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.ceofusion.org/ Website O
70 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Peter StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5V PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1J9 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Executive Title O
Director Title O
Bryan Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Watson Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
bwatson Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
ep Email I-EMAIL
- Email I-EMAIL
enterprises.com Email E-EMAIL

Cleantech Organization B-ORG
North Organization E-ORG
Environment TargetIndustry O
Private Governance O
Accelerator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.cleantechnorth.com Website O
None StreetAddress O
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
None PostalCode O
None Title O
Bryan Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Watson Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
647 Telephone B-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
668 Telephone I-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
1594 Telephone E-PHONE
bwatson Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
cleantechnorth.com Email E-EMAIL

Coalition Organization B-ORG
Music Organization E-ORG
Creative TargetIndustry O
Private Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.coalitionent.com Website O
1731 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Lawrence StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Ave StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
East StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M1R PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2X7 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Co Title O
- Title O
Founder Title O
Eric Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Lawrence Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
eric.lawrence Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
coalitionent.com Email E-EMAIL

Cossette Organization S-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Private Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.cossette.com Website O
32 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Atlantic StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Avenue StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M6 PostalCode B-ADDRESS
K PostalCode I-ADDRESS
1X8 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Vice Title O
President Title O
, Title O
Product Title O
and Title O
Technology Title O
Strategy Title O
Joe Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Dee Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
416 Telephone B-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
725 Telephone I-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
7389 Telephone E-PHONE
joe.dee Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
cossette.com Email E-EMAIL

Driven Organization B-ORG
Accelerator Organization I-ORG
Group Organization E-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Not Governance O
- Governance O
for Governance O
- Governance O
profit Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.http://drivenaccelerator.com/ Website O
376 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Bathurst StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5 PostalCode B-ADDRESS
T PostalCode I-ADDRESS
2S6 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
CEO Title O
Tamar Contact-LastName B-PERSON
- Contact-LastName I-PERSON
Melissa Contact-LastName E-PERSON
Huggins Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
drivenaccelerator Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
gmail.com Email E-EMAIL

Ember Organization B-ORG
Business Organization I-ORG
Exchange Organization E-ORG
Mixed TargetIndustry O
Private Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.emberbx.com Website O
1 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Yonge StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Suite Unit B-ADDRESS
2002 Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5E PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1E5 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Vice Title O
President Title O
, Title O
Operations Title O
Gail Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Gillian Contact-FirstName B-PERSON
- Contact-FirstName I-PERSON
Bain Contact-FirstName E-PERSON
None Telephone O
ggillian Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
tbdc.com Email E-EMAIL

Fasken Organization B-ORG
Martineau Organization I-ORG
LLPâ€ Organization I-ORG
™ Organization I-ORG
s Organization I-ORG
Start Organization I-ORG
- Organization I-ORG
up Organization I-ORG
and Organization I-ORG
Entrepreneurial Organization I-ORG
Development Organization I-ORG
Program Organization E-ORG
Mixed TargetIndustry O
Private Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.faskenstartup.com Website O
333 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Bay StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
St. StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Suite Unit B-ADDRESS
2400 Unit I-ADDRESS
, Unit I-ADDRESS
Box Unit I-ADDRESS
20 Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5H PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2T6 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
None Title O
None Contact-LastName O
None Contact-FirstName O
416 Telephone B-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
366 Telephone I-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
8381 Telephone E-PHONE
toronto Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
fasken.com Email E-EMAIL

Futurpreneur Organization S-ORG
Mixed TargetIndustry O
Not Governance O
- Governance O
for Governance O
- Governance O
profit Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.futurpreneur.ca Website O
133 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Richmond StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
St. StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
W. StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Suite Unit B-ADDRESS
700 Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5H PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2L3 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
CEO Title O
Julia Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Deans Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
jdeans Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
futurpreneur.ca Email E-EMAIL

Gizmo Organization B-ORG
Labs Organization E-ORG
Mixed TargetIndustry O
Private Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.gizmolabs.ca Website O
298 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Dundas StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
St. StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
W StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Level3 Unit S-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5 PostalCode B-ADDRESS
T PostalCode I-ADDRESS
1G2 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
None Title O
None Contact-LastName O
None Contact-FirstName O
( Telephone B-PHONE
416)-887 Telephone I-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
6683 Telephone E-PHONE
info Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
gizmolabs.ca Email E-EMAIL

HIGHLINE Organization S-ORG
Mixed TargetIndustry O
Information Governance O
, Governance O
Communications Governance O
and Governance O
Technology Governance O
Accelerator BusinessSupportType O
http://www Website O
. Website O
HIGHLINE.vc Website O
639 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Queen StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5V PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2B7 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Managing Title O
Director Title O
Marcus Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Daniels Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
speedtoseed Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
HIGHLINE.vc Email E-EMAIL

Humber Organization B-ORG
College Organization I-ORG
- Organization I-ORG
HumberLaunch Organization E-ORG
Mixed TargetIndustry O
Academia Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.humber.ca Website O
/ Website O
humberlaunch/ Website O
3180 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Lake StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Shore StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Blvd StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
W. StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M8V PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1L7 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Program Title O
Manager Title O
Cheryl Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Mitchell Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
cheryl.mitchell Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
humber.ca Email E-EMAIL

ideaBOOST Organization B-ORG
Canadian Organization I-ORG
Film Organization I-ORG
Centre Organization E-ORG
Creative TargetIndustry O
Not Governance O
- Governance O
for Governance O
- Governance O
profit Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.ideaboost.ca/ Website O
101 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
College StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Suite Unit B-ADDRESS
245 Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5 PostalCode B-ADDRESS
G PostalCode I-ADDRESS
1L7 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Chief Title O
Digital Title O
Officer Title O
Ana Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Serrano Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
aserrano Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
cfccreates.com Email E-EMAIL

Imagination Organization B-ORG
Catalyst Organization I-ORG
OCADU Organization E-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Academia Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.ocadu.ca Website O
/ Website O
research Website O
/ Website O
imaginationcatalyst.htm Website O
100 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
McCaul StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5 PostalCode B-ADDRESS
T PostalCode I-ADDRESS
1W1 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Director Title O
, Title O
Digital Title O
Futures Title O
Implementation Title O
Monica Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Contreras Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
mcontreras Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
ocadu.ca Email E-EMAIL

Incubes Organization B-ORG
Accelerator Organization E-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Private Governance O
Accelerator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.incubes.ca Website O
70 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Peter StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5V PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1J9 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
CEO Title O
Ben Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Zlotnick Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
ben Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
incubes.ca Email E-EMAIL

Innovation Organization B-ORG
York Organization I-ORG
- Organization I-ORG
York Organization I-ORG
University Organization E-ORG
Mixed TargetIndustry O
Academia Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.innovationyork.ca Website O
4700 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Keele StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Kaneff Unit B-ADDRESS
Tower Unit I-ADDRESS
, Unit I-ADDRESS
Fifth Unit I-ADDRESS
Floor Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M3J PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1P3 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Director Title O
Sarah Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Howe Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
( Telephone B-PHONE
416 Telephone I-PHONE
) Telephone I-PHONE
736 Telephone I-PHONE
2100 Telephone E-PHONE
showe Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
yorku.ca Email E-EMAIL

Italian Organization B-ORG
Chamber Organization I-ORG
of Organization I-ORG
Commerce Organization I-ORG
( Organization I-ORG
ICCO Organization I-ORG
) Organization E-ORG
Mixed TargetIndustry O
Not Governance O
- Governance O
for Governance O
- Governance O
profit Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.italchambers.ca Website O
622 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
College StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M6 PostalCode B-ADDRESS
G PostalCode I-ADDRESS
1B6 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Executive Title O
Director Title O
Italian Title O
Chamber Title O
of Title O
Commerce Title O
Corrado Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Paina Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
paina Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
italchambers.ca Email E-EMAIL

Kinetic Organization B-ORG
CafÃ Organization I-ORG
© Organization E-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Private Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.kineticcafe.com Website O
1 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Yonge StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
St StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Suite Unit B-ADDRESS
934 Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5E PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1E5 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Co Title O
- Title O
Founder Title O
Chris Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Carter Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
info Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
kineticcafe.com Email E-EMAIL

Launch Organization B-ORG
180 Organization I-ORG
Accelerator Organization E-ORG
Mixed TargetIndustry O
Not Governance O
- Governance O
for Governance O
- Governance O
profit Governance O
Accelerator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.launch180.com Website O
51 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Wolseley StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5 PostalCode B-ADDRESS
T PostalCode I-ADDRESS
1S1 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
None Title O
None Contact-LastName O
None Contact-FirstName O
+ Telephone B-PHONE
1 Telephone I-PHONE
888 Telephone I-PHONE
840 Telephone I-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
6668 Telephone E-PHONE
None Email O

Mantella Organization B-ORG
Venture Organization I-ORG
Partners Organization E-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Private Governance O
Accelerator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.mantellavp.com Website O
488 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Wellington StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
St StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
West StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5V PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1E3 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
None Title O
None Contact-LastName O
None Contact-FirstName O
416 Telephone B-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
479 Telephone I-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
0779 Telephone E-PHONE
info Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
mantellavp.com Email E-EMAIL

MaRS Organization B-ORG
Discovery Organization I-ORG
District Organization E-ORG
Mixed TargetIndustry O
Bio TargetIndustry O
- TargetIndustry O
Medical TargetIndustry O
Not Governance O
- Governance O
for Governance O
- Governance O
profit Governance O
Accelerator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.marsdd.com Website O
101 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
College StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Suite Unit B-ADDRESS
100 Unit I-ADDRESS
- Unit I-ADDRESS
South Unit I-ADDRESS
Tower Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5 PostalCode B-ADDRESS
G PostalCode I-ADDRESS
1L7 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Director Title O
, Title O
Strategic Title O
Partnerships Title O
Earl Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Miller Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
emiller Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
marsdd.com Email E-EMAIL

Mobile Organization B-ORG
Experience Organization I-ORG
Innovation Organization I-ORG
Centre Organization I-ORG
( Organization I-ORG
MEIC Organization I-ORG
) Organization E-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Not Governance O
- Governance O
for Governance O
- Governance O
profit Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.meic.ca Website O
205 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Richmond StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
St StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
West StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
2nd Unit B-ADDRESS
Floor Unit I-ADDRESS
, Unit I-ADDRESS
Room Unit I-ADDRESS
7211 Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5V PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1V3 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Director Title O
Patricia Contact-LastName S-PERSON
McCuthcheon Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
patricia Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
meic.ca Email E-EMAIL

MultiplicityTO Organization S-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Not Governance O
- Governance O
for Governance O
- Governance O
profit Governance O
Accelerator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.multiplicityaccelerator.com/ Website O
105 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Victoria StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Suite Unit B-ADDRESS
909 Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5C PostalCode B-ADDRESS
3B4 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Co Title O
- Title O
founder Title O
Rajah Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Lehal Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
rlehal Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
multiplicityaccelerator.com Email E-EMAIL

oneeleven Organization S-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Not Governance O
- Governance O
for Governance O
- Governance O
profit Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.oneeleven.com Website O
111 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Richmond StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
West StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5H PostalCode B-ADDRESS
3K6 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Managing Title O
Director Title O
Bilal Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Khan Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
Bilal Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
oneeleven.com Email E-EMAIL

Ontario Organization B-ORG
Centre Organization I-ORG
of Organization I-ORG
Excellence Organization I-ORG
( Organization I-ORG
OCE Organization I-ORG
) Organization E-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Public Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.oce Website O
- Website O
ontario.org Website O
156 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Front StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
West StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Suite Unit B-ADDRESS
200 Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5J PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2L6 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Business Title O
Development Title O
Manager Title O
Martin Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Lord Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
martin.lord Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
oce Email I-EMAIL
- Email I-EMAIL
ontario.org Email I-EMAIL
" Email I-EMAIL
" Email E-EMAIL

Rogers Organization B-ORG
Ventures Organization E-ORG
Mixed TargetIndustry O
Private Governance O
Accelerator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.rogersvp.com/ Website O
350 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Bloor StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
East StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M4W PostalCode B-ADDRESS
0A1 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Vice Title O
President Title O
Mike Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Lee Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
contact Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
rogersventures.com Email E-EMAIL

Round Organization B-ORG
13 Organization I-ORG
Capital Organization E-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Private Governance O
Accelerator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.round13capital.com Website O
51 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Mill StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Suite Unit B-ADDRESS
301 Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5A PostalCode B-ADDRESS
3C4 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Entrepreneur Title O
Bruce Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Croxon Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
contact Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
round13capital.com Email E-EMAIL

Ryerson Organization B-ORG
University Organization I-ORG
- Organization I-ORG
Centre Organization I-ORG
for Organization I-ORG
Urban Organization I-ORG
Energy Organization E-ORG
Environment TargetIndustry O
Academia Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.cue.ryerson.ca Website O
147 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Dalhousie StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5B PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2M7 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Director Title O
Bala Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Venkatesh Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
bala Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
ryerson.ca Email E-EMAIL

Ryerson Organization B-ORG
University Organization I-ORG
- Organization I-ORG
Digital Organization I-ORG
Media Organization I-ORG
Zone Organization E-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Academia Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.digitalmediazone.ryerson.ca Website O
10 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Dundas StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
East StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Ontario StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Suite Unit B-ADDRESS
600 Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5B PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2G9 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Director Title O
Valerie Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Fox Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
416 Telephone B-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
979 Telephone I-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
5000 Telephone E-PHONE
vfox Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
ryerson.ca Email E-EMAIL

Ryerson Organization B-ORG
University Organization I-ORG
- Organization I-ORG
Fashion Organization I-ORG
Zone Organization E-ORG
Fashion TargetIndustry O
Academia Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.fashionzone.ca/ Website O
10 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Dundas StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
St. StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
E. StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
B2 Unit B-ADDRESS
Floor Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5B PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2G9 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Managing Title O
Director Title O
Olga Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Okhrimenko Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
olga Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
fashionzone.ca Email E-EMAIL

Ryerson Organization B-ORG
University Organization I-ORG
- Organization I-ORG
Startmeup Organization I-ORG
Ryerson Organization E-ORG
Information TargetIndustry O
, TargetIndustry O
Communications TargetIndustry O
and TargetIndustry O
Technology TargetIndustry O
Academia Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.ryerson.ca Website O
/ Website O
rei Website O
/ Website O
startmeup_process/ Website O
575 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Bay StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
Ryerson Unit B-ADDRESS
University Unit I-ADDRESS
Ted Unit I-ADDRESS
Rogers Unit I-ADDRESS
School Unit I-ADDRESS
of Unit I-ADDRESS
Management Unit I-ADDRESS
TRS Unit I-ADDRESS
3 Unit I-ADDRESS
- Unit I-ADDRESS
139 Unit E-ADDRESS
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5 PostalCode B-ADDRESS
G PostalCode I-ADDRESS
2C5 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Director Title O
Valerie Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Fox Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
None Telephone O
vfox Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
ryerson.ca Email E-EMAIL

Ryerson Organization B-ORG
University Organization I-ORG
- Organization I-ORG
Transmedia Organization I-ORG
Zone Organization E-ORG
Mixed TargetIndustry O
Academia Governance O
Incubator BusinessSupportType O
http://www.rtatransmediacentre.com/ Website O
350 StreetAddress B-ADDRESS
Victoria StreetAddress I-ADDRESS
Street StreetAddress E-ADDRESS
None Unit O
Toronto City O
Ontario Province O
M5B PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2K3 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Director Title O
of Title O
Development Title O
Kathleen Contact-LastName S-PERSON
Webb Contact-FirstName S-PERSON
416 Telephone B-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
878 Telephone I-PHONE
- Telephone I-PHONE
8876 Telephone E-PHONE
kathleen.webb Email B-EMAIL
@ Email I-EMAIL
me.com Email E-EMAIL

