10101 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1991 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
11 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
07 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
Yes FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
GrowthWorks Company B-ORG
Canadian Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Ltd. Company E-ORG
None Website(Siteweb) O
5300 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
66 Street I-ADDRESS
Wellington Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street I-ADDRESS
West Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M5 PostalCode B-ADDRESS
K PostalCode I-ADDRESS
1E6 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Ian FundContact B-PERSON
Ross FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
934 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
7777 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10102 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1993 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
01 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
12 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
Yes FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
Dynamic Company B-ORG
Venture Company I-ORG
Opportunities Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Ltd. Company E-ORG
http://www.dynamic.ca Website(Siteweb) O
1 Street B-ADDRESS
Adelaide Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street I-ADDRESS
East Street I-ADDRESS
, Street I-ADDRESS
29th Street I-ADDRESS
Floor Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M5C PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2V9 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Ray FundContact B-PERSON
Benzinger FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
365 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
5113 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10103 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1993 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
12 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
17 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
The Company B-ORG
Active Company I-ORG
Communicatins Company I-ORG
Growth Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
None Website(Siteweb) O
2239 Street B-ADDRESS
Yonge Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M4S PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2B5 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
None FundContact O
None TelephoneNumber O

10104 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1993 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
12 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
17 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
Yes FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
Impax Company B-ORG
Venture Company I-ORG
Income Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
None Website(Siteweb) O
3740 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
181 Street I-ADDRESS
Bay Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M5J PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2T3 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Steve FundContact B-PERSON
Hawkins FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
601 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
2442 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10105 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1994 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
01 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
18 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
Yes FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
FESA Company B-ORG
Enterprise Company I-ORG
Venture Company I-ORG
Capital Company I-ORG
Fund Company E-ORG
None Website(Siteweb) O
None Street O
None City(Ville) O
None Province O
None PostalCode O
Les FundContact B-PERSON
Lyall FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
934 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
7777 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10106 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1994 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
08 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
31 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
Yes FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
Capital Company B-ORG
Alliance Company I-ORG
Ventures Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
http://www.cavi.com Website(Siteweb) O
600 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
60 Street I-ADDRESS
Queen Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street E-ADDRESS
Ottawa City(Ville) O
ON Province O
K1P PostalCode B-ADDRESS
5Y7 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Les FundContact B-PERSON
Lyall FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
-34 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
7777 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10108 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1994 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
10 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
11 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
Yes FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
Sportfund Company B-ORG
Inc Company E-ORG
None Website(Siteweb) O
None Street O
None City(Ville) O
None Province O
None PostalCode O
Daniel FundContact B-PERSON
Sobel FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
932 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
8300 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
x.6404 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10109 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1994 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
10 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
18 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
Trillium Company B-ORG
Growth Company I-ORG
Capital Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
None Website(Siteweb) O
None Street O
None City(Ville) O
None Province O
None PostalCode O
Les FundContact B-PERSON
Lyall FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
934 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
7777 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10112 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1994 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
12 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
14 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
TCU Company B-ORG
Development Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc Company E-ORG
None Website(Siteweb) O
None Street O
None City(Ville) O
None Province O
None PostalCode O
None FundContact O
None TelephoneNumber O

10113 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1994 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
01 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
18 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
First Company B-ORG
Ontario Company I-ORG
Labour Company I-ORG
Sponsored Company I-ORG
Investment Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Ltd Company E-ORG
http://www.firstontariofund.com Website(Siteweb) O
310 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
234 Street I-ADDRESS
Eglinton Street I-ADDRESS
Avenue Street I-ADDRESS
East Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M4P PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1K5 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Les FundContact B-PERSON
Lyall FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
934 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
7777 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10114 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1994 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
10 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
11 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
Yes FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
Retrocom Company B-ORG
Growth Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
http://www.rgfjobs.com Website(Siteweb) O
400 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
135 Street I-ADDRESS
Queens Street I-ADDRESS
Plate Street I-ADDRESS
Drive Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M9W PostalCode B-ADDRESS
6V1 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Daniel FundContact B-PERSON
Sobel FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
-32 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
8300 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10115 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1996 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
01 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
12 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
Tourism Company B-ORG
& Company I-ORG
Entertainment Company I-ORG
Growth Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
None Website(Siteweb) O
None Street O
None City(Ville) O
None Province O
None PostalCode O
None FundContact O
None TelephoneNumber O

10117 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1996 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
09 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
20 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
Yes FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
Canadian Company B-ORG
Science Company I-ORG
& Company I-ORG
Technology Company I-ORG
Growth Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
http://www.cstgf.com Website(Siteweb) O
2006 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
148 Street I-ADDRESS
Fullarton Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street E-ADDRESS
London City(Ville) O
ON Province O
N6A PostalCode B-ADDRESS
5P3 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Les FundContact B-PERSON
Lyall FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
934 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
7777 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10118 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1996 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
10 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
18 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
Innovacap Company B-ORG
Capital Company I-ORG
Corporation Company E-ORG
None Website(Siteweb) O
None Street O
None City(Ville) O
None Province O
None PostalCode O
None FundContact O
None TelephoneNumber O

10119 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1996 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
12 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
17 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
No FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
The Company B-ORG
Business Company I-ORG
, Company I-ORG
Engineering Company I-ORG
, Company I-ORG
Science Company I-ORG
& Company I-ORG
Technology Company I-ORG
Discoveries Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
http://www.bestfunds.ca Website(Siteweb) O
400 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
15 Street I-ADDRESS
Toronto Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M5C PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2E3 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
John FundContact B-PERSON
Richardson FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
203 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
7331 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
x.228 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10120 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1997 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
01 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
16 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
York Company B-ORG
Labour Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc Company E-ORG
http://www.lawrenceasset.com Website(Siteweb) O
1500 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
70 Street I-ADDRESS
York Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M5J PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1S9 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Miles FundContact B-PERSON
Nagamatsu FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
646 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
6292 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10121 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1999 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
10 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
20 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
Covington Company B-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
II Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
http://www.covington.ca Website(Siteweb) O
400 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
87 Street I-ADDRESS
Front Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street I-ADDRESS
East Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M5E PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1B8 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Phil FundContact B-PERSON
Reddon FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
365 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
0060 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10123 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
1999 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
11 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
30 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
New Company B-ORG
Millennium Company I-ORG
Venture Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
http://www.triaxcapital.com Website(Siteweb) O
1400 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
70 Street I-ADDRESS
York Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M5J PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1S9 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Phil FundContact B-PERSON
Reddon FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
365 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
0060 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10124 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
2000 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
11 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
29 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
New Company B-ORG
Generation Company I-ORG
Biotech Company I-ORG
( Company I-ORG
Equity Company I-ORG
) Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
http://www.triaxcapital.com Website(Siteweb) O
400 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
87 Street I-ADDRESS
Front Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street I-ADDRESS
West Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M5E PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1B8 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Phil FundContact B-PERSON
Reddon FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
365 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
0060 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10125 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
2000 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
11 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
29 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
New Company B-ORG
Generation Company I-ORG
Biotech Company I-ORG
( Company I-ORG
Balanced Company I-ORG
) Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
http://www.triaxcapital.com Website(Siteweb) O
1400 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
70 Street I-ADDRESS
York Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M5J PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1S9 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Phil FundContact B-PERSON
Reddon FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
365 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
0060 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10127 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
2000 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
11 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
29 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
GrowthWorks Company B-ORG
Opportunity Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Ltd. Company E-ORG
http://www.growthworks.ca Website(Siteweb) O
3504 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
20 Street I-ADDRESS
Queen Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street I-ADDRESS
West Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M5H PostalCode B-ADDRESS
3R3 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Les FundContact B-PERSON
Lyall FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
934 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
7777 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10130 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
2001 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
11 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
23 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
Yes FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
E2 Company B-ORG
Venture Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
http://www.triaxcapital.com Website(Siteweb) O
1400 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
70 Street I-ADDRESS
York Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M5J PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1S9 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Phil FundContact B-PERSON
Reddon FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
365 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
0060 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10131 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
2001 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
11 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
23 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
Axis Company B-ORG
Investment Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
http://www.bestfunds.ca Website(Siteweb) O
400 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
15 Street I-ADDRESS
Toronto Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M5C PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2E3 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
John FundContact B-PERSON
Richardson FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
203 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
7331 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
x.228 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10132 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
2001 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
11 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
23 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
Yes FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
Lawrence Company B-ORG
Enterprise Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
None Website(Siteweb) O
92 Street B-ADDRESS
Foxtail Street I-ADDRESS
Court Street E-ADDRESS
Georgetown City(Ville) O
ON Province O
L7 PostalCode B-ADDRESS
G PostalCode I-ADDRESS
0G2 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Matthew FundContact B-PERSON
Hoang FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
712 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
7456 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10133 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
2001 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
11 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
29 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
Yes FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
VentureLink Company B-ORG
Innovation Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
http://www.venturelinkfunds.com Website(Siteweb) O
602 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
3 Street I-ADDRESS
Church Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M5E PostalCode B-ADDRESS
1M2 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Geoff FundContact B-PERSON
Horton FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
681 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
6372 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10134 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
2001 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
12 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
12 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
CMDF Company B-ORG
Early Company I-ORG
Stage Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
http://www.cmdf.com Website(Siteweb) O
2006 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
148 Street I-ADDRESS
Fullarton Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street E-ADDRESS
London City(Ville) O
ON Province O
N6A PostalCode B-ADDRESS
5P3 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Steve FundContact B-PERSON
Hawkins FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
601 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
2442 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

10135 RegistrationNumber(Numérod'enregistrement) O
2001 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
12 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
- RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
12 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
00:00:00 RegistrationDate(Dated'enregistrement) O
None FederalRegistration(Enregistrementfédéral) O
Canadian Company B-ORG
Medical Company I-ORG
Discoveries Company I-ORG
Fund Company I-ORG
II Company I-ORG
Inc. Company E-ORG
None Website(Siteweb) O
3740 Street B-ADDRESS
- Street I-ADDRESS
181 Street I-ADDRESS
Bay Street I-ADDRESS
Street Street E-ADDRESS
Toronto City(Ville) O
ON Province O
M5J PostalCode B-ADDRESS
2T3 PostalCode E-ADDRESS
Steve FundContact B-PERSON
Hawkins FundContact E-PERSON
416 TelephoneNumber B-PHONE
601 TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
- TelephoneNumber I-PHONE
2442 TelephoneNumber E-PHONE

